Thank you for watching!
Thanks for all the hot water happy!
Hello! This time I'll be talking with Marin Fukuda from Tsubaki Factory and Miu Ishii from Tsubaki Factory!
Please stay with us until the end of this episode.
This is Miu's first time to be an MC for Halo! Please introduce yourself.
I'm Miyu Ishii, a new member of Tsubaki Factory, a 15-year-old first-year high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture.
My hobby is to watch red panda's threat and my special skill is to bend only my little finger.
I'd like to ask you a few questions about your self-introductions, but there are a few things that caught my attention.
First of all, I was wondering about your special skill.
Bending only your little finger?
What? That's amazing.
I've never heard of that before... but it's a unique skill.
I think it's very good.
Please do it.
This was written in the script, so let me ask you something.
I'm sorry to ask, but you mentioned me as someone you admire.
May I ask what you think of me?
I fell in love with you because of your voice
Your voice is so different from the way you sing when you perform You usually have a gentle aura about you, but when you perform you can be so cool or so cute
I'm sorry I made you say that, but now that you've said it, I'd like to talk a little bit about my impression of Sanwa-chan, too.
I'd like to talk a little bit about my impression of Sanbane.
She's so friendly that I want to take her as a sister.
Her actions and words are always so cute.
I'm always moved by her actions and words.
And in terms of performance, I've always loved Hello Project and Tsubaki Factory.
I think it's because of her love for Hello Project and Tsubaki Factory.
I was surprised to see that the level of your performance is much higher than when I joined the group as a new member.
I'm often surprised by their high level of performance.
Thank you very much.
Now, please watch this video.
Here you go.
Here is the second one.
Here comes the third one.
Here we go.
Here comes the last one.
Okay, you're all set.
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
He's a cute dog.
Look at him, everyone.
Cute.
Bottom time.
Well then, it's BINGOS OF DREAMS first and last, one-time-only live performance,
Let's give a performance that will make a lot of people You Happy.
Yes, sir.
Eh, fumee.
Yes, let's, uh, cherish the world view of each and every song,
I think BEYOND's strength is that each song is completely different,
I think it's BEYOND's strength to be completely different from each other.
We will express the girl of YUHA as much as we can,
Let's express the BEYOND style with all our might using the conditions.
May I conclude? One word.
Yes, I'm nervous.
I'm nervous.
But YUHA, get used to BEYOND.
Get used to it. I got used to it.
I'm glad.
Let's do our best.
Yes.
Ready.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Se-no.
Let's go BEYOND!
I'm not used to this. I'm not used to it.
I'm not used to it. I'm not used to it.
Put it back, put it back.
I'm not used to this.
It's still okay.
Bon appétit.
Please take care of it.
Pleasure to meet you.
Morning and now today, a story about a girl's Kai.
I would like to share with you a story about a girl named Koihana no Isseki.
The time is the summer of 2024
On a platform of any station
Two high school girls chatting with each other
Yuhane, let's confess to Kyoko's boy with glasses
I can't.
Because I don't know anything about him except that he wears glasses
You're in love, right?
Yes, I am.
Holding out for love is a waste of youth
But you might have a girlfriend, Glasses.
You're in love, aren't you?
I am.
Beven.
Then came the rivals.
Two young ladies who look like ladies.
How do you do?
Shimakura-san, you're on time for the train.
I wonder if she made it to the train on time wearing her glasses.
Oh, my God, Karah!
I wonder if this young lady is Glasses-boy's train...
I'm no match for the warlike Miss. No, I'll win this war.
Why, real ladies don't ride crowded trains.
Nice. Glasses train's here.
What? Where's the rival prince? Don't miss the train, we're going in.
We're jammed in again today, number two.
You'll see that girl you've been eyeing in your usual spot on the train.
You know, the guy in the glasses whose name I don't even know.
Hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
Same car, same time.
me
ni
ni ni
A boy with a nice face
Oh, glasses. The boy with the glasses.
Please take them off.
I want to see your last face
The boy with the glass veil
Oh, the boy with the glasses, the glasses.
Please take them off.
I want to see your last face.
The boy with the glass veil
And a sudden brake. A sudden stop.
It's a full stop, so everyone pushes like they just did.
Oops, I know it's a holiday, but I'll take it.
a boy with glasses in front of me today
holding me in his arms and pulling in my breath
please let the time stand still
but the train's starting to move
a boy with glasses pulling away from me
a boy with a kind face
oh, a boy with glasses, glasses
Please take them off me
I want to see your summer face
The boy with the glass veil
Oh, the boy with the glasses
Please take it off me
I want to see your summer face
How long has it been since
I used to see you every morning
I wonder if you've moved somewhere else
I find myself looking for the color of today
I'll be looking for the color
I was late that day and got on just in time
Happy game in a different car than usual
To the gas club where we were supposed to leave
All your heart
I never thought I'd see you without your glasses
You're fresh, you've changed, you're next to me
Who's that girl smiling so prettily?
Don't tell me you're holding hands too?
A boy with a kind face
But his glasses are now contacts.
They're getting old, so I took them off
Happiness spills out
The boy with the empty face
But his glasses are now contacts
Empty boy
It's no big deal
Thanks for your work
This is Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory
and Mihane Ishii of Tsubaki Factory.
We'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
so don't think too much and answer at a quick pace.
Yes, ma'am.
Tell me Ishii Mihane's instruction manual.
If you show me the Hello Project video and the Lesser Panda video.
I'll be very happy.
Member color is white.
What does white mean to you, Mibane?
Daifuku.
What do you think I have the best among the members of Tsubaki Factory?
The amount of hair I have.
What is your favorite dish?
Cooking with rice cakes.
Mihane Ishii, 15 years old, what are your ambitions for the future?
I would like to work with a smile on my face and do my best to make my fans smile, too.
I think that was a very nice answer.
I would like to ask you a few questions that caught my attention.
I would like to ask you a few questions that I was curious about.
Daifuku? Daifuku?
Do you like rice cakes and Japanese sweets?
I love them.
I see.
The sticky ones.
Mochi-mochi wagashi.
Mochi is good.
So, do you prefer Japanese sweets or Western sweets?
Wagashi.
I never knew that. I'm glad I bought it.
Let's go eat Daifuku next time.
I'd love to!
Yes, and on your ambition for the future...
I think the word "smile" was a bit characteristic.
I think the word "smile" was a bit characteristic of you.
I want to do my best with a smile on my face.
If I don't smile, I don't think many people will smile either, so I want to do my best to keep smiling.
I think that's very nice. I hope you will continue to do your best with a smile on your face.
Ms. Fukuda, the picture question will come after the VTR.
Hello! Sta.
Hallo! Ste.
BEYOND Hi2Diamond Now on sale!
Go City Coop, Now on sale!
BEYONDZ HOOK's Law
Now on sale!
BEYONDZ LIVE TOUR 2024
Spring Personality
WINGS OF DREAMS
It's over!
It was fun!
Oh no.
Maybe.
It was my first
I think everyone was wondering what kind of concert it would be,
But, like Muguha's graduation concert, everyone was laughing the whole time,
It was very much like Yuhane, and it turned out to be a great concert and a lot of fun.
It was a great concert and a lot of fun. Thank you very much.
How was it?
I think there have been many graduation concerts in the past.
Project's history.
Project has never had a graduation concert before.
How was it, Kine?
It was a really good day!
Today was something!
Not only the beautiful skin, but everyone was shining as Miyons,
And the people in the bar who were watching over us were also shining in red,
I really think that the tooth pit was the most sparkling place in the world today!
Thank you everyone, everyone and everyone for a truly wonderful day!
Thank you very much!
I don't see Necchan right now, but I'm sure the 10 of us will continue to do our best in the future, and I'm sure you'll all be proud of us.
How about you, Mr. Masaki, who has flown away today?
Well, it all happened so fast, each song is the last, right?
I know that, but I didn't feel that way.
And I had the feeling that I wanted to keep going, but when everyone commented on YUHA at the end, they all expressed their feelings in a very honest way.
They were very honest and gave us a lot of nice words that we could have drawn out from anywhere.
If it weren't for Miyons, I don't think YUHA would have been able to express her feelings so honestly.
I don't think YUHA would have been able to express her feelings so honestly if she had not been in Miyons.
I thought that if it weren't for Miyons, YUHA wouldn't have been able to express her feelings so openly and honestly.
That is why I feel that YUHA has grown up in many aspects as a figure of Japan.
This concert was a great opportunity for me to reflect on my growth.
I think this concert was a great opportunity for me to show my growth to all of you who are supporting me.
I think this concert became such a concert where I was able to show my growth to all of you who support me.
I was so happy!
Thank you very much.
For having a roof over our heads like that.
Just, you know, we're happy too.
We're happy.
So, from now on, we're going to go to Beyond 10 and do our best,
From here, I'm talking about IF,
I know that the seniors are reaching a milestone,
I think it's because the seniors are reaching milestones, and the OG members are coming to the school,
And at that moment, there was also some kind of match, right?
If that happened,
Yu-chan?
You said you would come.
What?
Here?
You're asking me here?
Are you sure?
Yes, it's okay.
It's fine.
But it's an eternity, right?
Yes, it is.
That's why,
Let's play again.
Okay.
I'd like to join you then.
Please come and play with us.
Please continue to support BEYOND and Haru Yamazaki as they do their best in the future.
Thank you very much.
That's all for BEYOND.
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Fukuda a question.
Yes, please.
Please do.
What do you think has changed the most since you joined Tsubaki Factory three years ago?
I am now able to express myself.
In May this year, Tsubaki Factory held a concert in Shanghai, where Fukuda was born and raised.
What were your honest feelings at that time?
I was very moved.
What would you like to celebrate with Mr. Fukuda and I, whose birthdays are two days apart?
I would like to celebrate together with a coke wallaby and a red panda doll.
What would you call the three new members of Tsubaki Factory?
Mihamiha, Foo Foo, and You Foo.
Please tell us in your favorite English words that best fit Tsubaki Factory's current 11-member lineup.
Yes, I do.
Kudo kuru kuru kuru b. Better. Thank you very much.
If you say so, I'll have to sentence Fukuoka for wanting to play with Mr. Raby and Mr. Lesser Panda.
We both like animals in common, and we both like fluffy things, so if we can celebrate our birthdays together...
So when we decided to celebrate our birthdays together, I thought it would be nice to do it in a place where we could be surrounded by all our favorite things.
That's very nice. I'd like to do that.
And one more thing, how would you describe the Tsubaki Factory in English?
Well, I couldn't be better.
I often think that the current Tsubaki Factory is very impressive.
I think there are a lot of things to see in the current Tsudzuki Factory.
I couldn't help but think that it's the time when everyone is trying to get more powerful after Shinnuma-san's graduation.
I think it's a time when we have a lot of momentum and we couldn't be better.
It's difficult to translate directly into Japanese, but I think it means "the best".
I think we are in the best condition right now.
I chose "couldn't be better".
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much. We'll continue after this.
100,000 yen!
Well, it's the first day of the show!
I'm very nervous, but let's have fun!
Yes! Ready!
Airey!
Lil! From here!
Rihane!
Rehane is my real name!
Cute teeth!
Honda!
They're all suddenly coming together!
Let's go, Doika!
nee!!!
Yikes!
I want a crosswind, meine!
3, 2, 1, GO!
dewy bear de ran dewy bear
no change at once
Yes, I'm going to make a cluster
Effort!
Grillo!
Siwire ha hako!
Iwaki or
voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice voice
Hakaritta just go!
Oh p entry!
Oh!
What are you doing?
A single word is your partner, and it falls deep into your eyes.
Why do you do that word and the other person?
Why do you do that word and the other?
Why do you do it with that word?
When you are doing the same thing in another Is that what this app is called?
I'm not sure what this app is called?
This heads up fantastic!
What does this app also mean?
What does this app mean too?
I know what I'm doing and I know what I'm doing.
I miss you so much.
I'm nowhere to be found
Just you
Don't be just like a fantastic show
Ah Ah Ah Ah, as time goes by
Every time I grow up
I feel fragile and unstable
The weight of memories
When I can't bear it
Because you were there, I was able to shine
Meteors cut through the night sky
Somewhere you are there too
Words like that
I'm so clumsy
But thank you for watching over me
Thank you for watching over me
Love is like an orthography
A telepathic connection for the sake of
No matter how silent or hidden it may be
You are nowhere to be found
Just you
To everyone I love
I met someone who told me they love my singing
I love singing even more and more
I met someone who likes my quirky personality
I met someone who said she loved my quirky personality
I decided to be myself
I met someone who was happy to hear my happy report
I met someone who was happy to hear my happy report as if it were their own
When I imagine them being happy
I was able to do my best many times over.
I met someone who found me even though I was a reclusive person
I became a greedy person who wanted to be seen more and more
Everyone's presence has made my everyday life
I love the red color of your presence.
Thank you for meeting me
I hope that someday you will remember those days
I hope that my presence will be included in your memories someday.
Rika
Rikchan
Sayatan
Kurumin
Kokoro
Mimi
Hime-chan
Mio
Koba
Woo
My favorite name that I called many times
I met irreplaceable and irreplaceable friends
I was lonely when I moved to Tokyo
I now have someone who is like a family
We share the same joys, the same worries, the same pleasures
I met friends who share the same feelings
And when those feelings are combined
I learned that I could overcome any obstacle
I met friends who cried for me
I take a new step forward
The warmth of the hand that pushed me back made me promise not to give in
My friends have made my everyday life colorful and rainbow-colored
Thank you for meeting me
And the staff who always support me
To everyone involved
Thank you for watching
Manager
I learned that every encounter
I learned that every encounter has a positive meaning.
Being able to work in Hello Project, which I have always dreamed of
It is my good luck charm from now on.
I can proudly say that my righteous youth was here.
I can proudly say
Today
Surrounded by everyone I love in this place overflowing with love
I am the happiest bird in the galaxy
Here's a phrase
Spread the wings of my dreams and let's fly, biyon, biyon, biyon, biyon
Gia Marie Wow!
Today, June 27th
I, Yuhane Yamazaki
I'm spreading my wings toward a new dream
Lyrics, music, arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Before I become a memory
I can't wait to meet you and tell you
I was such a little girl
Thank you for finding me
Love is like a caretaker tree
Sometimes it's just a pinch short
Long and short and short and short and short
I miss you and there's no one else
Only you, only you
Thank you for pulling the strings of fate
Even if it's just by chance
Even if it's just for a moment
Tomorrow and the next day and the day after that
I'll never forget you.
Please, I promise.
Dadda peacher.
Dadda peecher.
Daddapiction.
Dadda Pichon
Mabayashi Fukuda and Mihane Ishii of Tsubaki Factory present "Halo! Stay!
We'd like you to get to know Mibane a little better, so we'd like to dig a little deeper.
I'd like to dig a little deeper.
Yes, we asked her to write down her favorite things in her sketchbook, so let's talk while looking at them.
So let's talk while looking at them.
Let's open the sketchbook.
Wow!
They wrote a lot of things in the sketchbook.
First of all, I'm very interested in socks.
Socks?
I really like collecting socks.
I see.
I don't get to see socks as much as I do clothes.
That's true.
I really like patterned socks.
I buy them as soon as I think they're cute.
I buy them.
In terms of socks...
One time, I got a pair of socks from Minani, too.
She gave me a pair of socks
that says "Fukuda's Fortune" on it.
Why did you buy them for me?
Clothes
I could only think of Mr. Fukuda's clothes
I originally had one, and I happened to keep it
I thought I'd like you to wear them together
I wear them a lot
Thank you very much.
Next, towels
Towels get cold.
You know, people who like collectibles collect a lot of things
Towels.
They come in all kinds of patterns.
Yes, there are.
Hello Project goods are one example.
I see.
You collect all kinds of patterns.
Once I start collecting them, I can't stop.
I can't stop.
Please send me a picture next time.
Next...
I'm also interested in your bangs.
Yes, why?
Your bangs are so beautiful and straight.
I especially like the one centimeter under your eyebrow.
One centimeter under the eyebrow?
Just by looking at her bangs, I get the feeling that she is Akiyama.
Wow, I'm looking at Akiyama-san from a new perspective.
Hello! Sta.
Yes, and there is a red panda...
Yes...
Then, can you tell us how you came to like red pandas?
I saw a video of a red panda and it was a video of a red panda threatening a red panda.
I really like red pandas because they are threatening, but I can't help but think they are cute, and they are so soft and fuzzy.
I also like the short hands of the red panda.
I like all dogs, big and small.
Do you have a dog? Yes, I have a dog. A toy poodle.
Toypuddles are so fluffy and cute, they're so adorable.
And then doughnuts. I love doughnuts because they're round and they have holes in them.
That's nice. I love anything sweet.
And I love the texture of the fluff. I love the fluff.
I love the fluffy texture. I've never heard of fluffy texture.
I've never heard of fluffy texture before, but it's definitely fluffy.
I happened to buy some doughnuts for Mihari-chan today.
I'm glad they were round and open in the middle.
I guessed the view.
You wrote Hello Project first. Is there anything you want to talk about Hello Project?
Well, Hello Project is about dancing, but I think that even though you're singing and dancing, your singing voice isn't blurred.
And I also like the way you guys look when you're dancing or performing.
I was really attracted to them because they were all so cool. I know, I'm attracted to the Halo Project in the same way.
I know that you are also attracted to Halo Project, so I'm going to do my best to be one of the cool members. Please leave a message for those who are reading "Halo!
Yes, I just joined the group.
I've just joined the group, so I think there are still a lot of things I don't know.
I'd like you to know a lot of things about me from now on.
Haloste!
This is Haroste with Marin Fukuda and Mihane Ishii from Tsubaki Factory.
and Mihane Ishii of Tsubaki Factory
It's time to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement.
We, Tsubaki Factory, will be releasing a new single on August 28th, our first release in 11 months.
This single is a triple-ensemble single, and it includes three songs: Baby Spider, Seishun Ekusabai, and Kodo Oujia.
All three songs have different charms and are very worth listening to, so please get a lot of them!
Project 2024 Summer All of Us
Project, so please come and enjoy the show!
And now, Tsubaki Factory is going to perform at Tokyo Idol Festival 2024!
Yes, Tsubaki Factory will be performing on Sunday, August 4th!
Tokyo Idol Festival is a festival where various idols perform every year.
We will do our best to show you the charm of Tsubaki Factory and Tsubaki Factory alone.
Please come and join us!
And on August 29th, Tsubaki Factory will be holding its Summer Festival 2024 Scorching Heat at Kawaguchiko Stella Theater.
We will be doing some things that we don't usually do at concerts, so please look forward to it!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to our channel.
This time, we had two members of Tsubaki Factory, Marin Fukuda and Mihane Ishii.
Good bye.
And now, the last number by the 11 of us.
Please listen to it.
Nobishiro Beyond the World
But it's going to be okay, but it's going to be okay, but it's going to be okay
Every time I feel anxious, we go back and forth.
Thank you for watching!
I'm a mind
I travel
Silhouette stretching into the sunset
Riglets flapping ahead
I still can't say with a smile that I miss
Every day is a slacker
Things I can't do, I'm so tired
A day goes by so fast
I have room to grow
I've got room to grow
Nothing's over yet
It's just beginning
Hey baby
Let's laugh
Let's smile for the dents
Hey baby
What an aded resume
here
många
Dean
me
Beach
man
You're the only one
You'll find yourself smiling again
You have room to grow
You're the one who makes me feel like I can do something.
You're the one who makes me feel like I can do something
Grow. I have room to grow
♪ You've got room to grow
Spread your wings
With you spreading your wings
Be your the world
um um ah am uh
I'm still the same person I was that day
The tears that wouldn't stop will turn into smiles someday, won't they?
Don't worry! I'm sure this road stretches into the future!
Don't get all neat and small
Transform freely like water into itself
Tired of it all, jump over yourself
Grow up, because we have room to grow up
We're not finished yet, we're just getting started
Grow up, because we have room to grow
We can't go anywhere
Use this door to spread out
With you flapping your wings
You'll be here
Grow, for we have room to grow
Nothing's finished yet, it's just beginning
Grow
We've got
We have room to grow
Grow
Because we have
We have it
Spread it out through this door
With your eyes
With you in a huddle
Be with you
Be You
The World
monday
Starring Break
Master
Wada-Ya
Venue
Mix
side dish
Wrestler
princess
hate
Never
Not finished
enough
I am
two
Thank you for your hard work.
John graduated from BEYOND and Hello! Project.
Thank you so much to everyone who has always supported us.
I am very happy to have been a part of Hello! Project, I was a trainee of Alfalu, a member of Hello! Project as a fan of the show since before I became a trainee member of Alfal,
This is a personal matter,
I am a fan of the Hello! Project before I became a trainee.
Project, I was a fan of the show even before I became a trainee, and it was a personal matter for me,
I saw them all working so hard, and that's how I got into the group,
I was also the reason why I wanted to be a Halo Pro trainee. I hope I can be a catalyst for idols who are watching Halo!
I'm looking forward to seeing them again as fans,
I'm looking forward to seeing you again as a fan.
I received so much love from everyone.
I am rehappy. Thank you very much.